《越狱》前情回顾
previously on prison break
呆这别动 别出声
Stay here, stay here.Stay quiet.
农场的房子已经不见了  迈克
The ranch is gone, Michael.
我们必须做点什么
We gotta do something,
但是一定不能伤害到别人
and it's not going to involve hurting you.
我有个计划
I got an idea.
夫人  非常抱歉打扰你
Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
你家是不是没电了
Is your electricity out?
这些罪犯一定在这其中的某个小镇里
Those cons are in one of these towns
不可能逃出方圆64英里的范围
and couldn't have gone further than 64 miles in any direction.
我要知道在这个半径范围内的一切事情
I want everything you've got in that perimeter.
老实说  呃...
Well, to be honest, uh...
我想给总统简短的汇报下
I was expecting to brief the president.
你向我汇报吧！
You report to me now.
直说吧 现在我们面临最大的问题是
Frankly, the biggest issue we have to address
你的女儿面临的指控
are the charges facing your daughter.
很高兴见到你  先生
Good to meet you, sir.
莎拉
Sara
你还记得我在你公寓见到的那个男的吗?
Do you remember that guy that I met with you in your apartment?
我想你还是离他远点
I want you to stay away from him.
你在说什么啊?
What are you talking about?
那是哪里啊?
Where is that?
荷兰
It's Holland.
真漂亮
It's beautiful.
这个是汽油钱
And that's for the car.
一个小时以后我们在这里等你回来
We'll meet you right back here in an hour.
把手举起来放在头后面  跪下
put your hands behind your head and drop to your knees.
哦  天那
Oh, god.
你个臭婊子  别发出声音
Don't say a word, you little fool
否则割断你的喉咙
or I'm gonna cut your throat out.
求你了!
Ah! Oh, please!
你再发出声音试试
You try that again,
我让你的喉咙开个洞
I'll pry those vocal chords right out of your throat.
她来做什么?
What's she doing?
她过来了
She's coming up here.
别过来  别过来!
Stay there, stay there.
妈妈  你在家吗?
Mom, you home?
妈
Mom?
放松，放松
It's ok,It's ok.
退后  把手举起来
back away and put your hands up.
放松!
Just go easy.
怕什么
Go nothing.
她手里又没有王牌
She ain't the one carrying the cards here.
退后把手举起来
Back away and put your hands up.
我举起手
I put my hand up,
就会把他的喉管拉出来
I'll take her jugular with it.
我不想任何人做傻事  明白吗?
I don't want anyone to do anything stupid, okay?
别动
Don't move.
让我们文明点
uh! Let's be civil here.
别挣扎了  放松
Stop.Relax.
你可以走了
You can go.
花具店的人说布伦斯强得和猩猩一样
Guy at the garden center said Burrows was strong as a gorilla.
他们被绑住的时候正好是一点钟
It was 1:00 P.M.When they tangled it up.
他认出了斯科菲尔德和布伦斯
The guy id'd both of them--Scofield, Burrows.
非常确定
No doubt about it in his mind.
当然  假定是一点钟
Of course, given that was 1:00 P.M.,
那么他们现在已经在300英里外了
Those two could be 300 miles from here by now.
你难道没发现，店里少了很多锄、铁锹和电动工具
You have a half a dozen picks
shovels and power tools missing from that store.
他们还在这里  他们正在挖
They're here and they're digging.
500万美元
Five million dollars
就埋在图勒镇的某个地方
buried somewhere beneath the streets of Tooele.
你真的相信?
You really believe that?
他们相信  这个才重要
They believe that,and that's the important thing.
他们现在可能在任何地方
They could be anywhere now.
我们没有足够的警力
We don't have the units
挨家挨户去搜查
to go door-to-door.
我们不需要
We won't need them.
他会告诉我们去哪里找
He's going to tell us where to look.
太有趣了  我刚刚想联系你
It's so funny,I was just about to text you.
今天是你的幸运日 是吗?
Today's your lucky day.Is it?
是的  我的阿姨马克辛终于给了我
Yeah, my aunt Maxine finally gave me
她拿手的巧克力小甜饼的秘方
her famous chocolate chip cookie recipe
如果你今晚有空
and if you're free tonight,
我很荣幸地邀请你做我的豚鼠（指试验品）
I'd love for you to be my guinea pig.
哦...不行
Uh... I can'T.
今天晚上不行
Not tonight.
别这样
Come on.
我怎么听就象丹尼尔唱的歌
You sound just like Daniel.
今晚不行 真的不行 －你知道吗?
Not tonight.Not tonight.You know what?
如果你不介意  我真的要走了
If you don't mind,I've actually gotta go.
哦...
Oh...
你还好吗?
are you okay?
我是说你的推车还空着呢
I mean, your cart's empty.
我很好  谢谢  我要走了
I'm good. Thanks. Just gotta go.
莎拉
Sara.
这不太妙啊
This is going wrong in every possible way.
这样做太蠢了 伙计 我们不能这么做
This is stupid, man.We can not do this.
事情已经这样了
Hat's over the wall now.
你他妈的到底什么意思啊?
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
我的意思是我们已经在犯罪了
I mean we committed.
那么我们就一不做二不休
It's time to go get the hat.
我们没的选择
We don't have a choice.
我们有  我们可以离开
Yeah, we do.We can walk right up
马上离开这里  伙计
out of here right now, man.
那么然后怎么办?
And then what?
我们已经在这间屋子里了
We are already in the house.
两个女的也被绑了
Those women are bound.
我们已经犯罪了
We have already committed this crime.
我们离开   不能改变已经我们已经犯罪的事实
We leave, it ain't gonna change any of that.
为什么就不能只有地窖
Why couldn't there just be a silo
在空旷无人的田里呢? 在一个人迹罕至的地方
in the middle of a field with no one around?
我们想想办法
We'll figure it out.
我们可以用另一种方法拿钱
We can get the money another way.
是的 也许我可以再去抢另一家银行
Yeah, maybe I can rob another bank.
你知道查尔斯曾经告诉过我
You know what Charles once said to me?
罪犯就是罪犯  这罪责你甩也甩不掉
He said there's no such thing as an ex-con.
因为我以前一直认为
Because I used to think
我们有办法洗清冤屈
there was a way we could wipe the slate clean,
使我们所做的一切合情合理
make up for everything we've done.
事情已经发生了  林肯
The hat's over the wall, Linc.
对每个人都是
For everyone.
现在说句对不起  对你们来说可能一点意义都没有
"Sorry" isn't going to mean anything to you right now,
但我还是想说
but I want to say it anyway.
这原本不该发生
This wasn't supposed to happen.
再挖一两个小时我们就会走的
One or two hours tops and we'll be out of here,
我可以保证
and you have my word,
没有人会伤害你们
no one will harm you.
提高警惕注意点  好吗?
Keep your eyes open, okay?
不许伤害她们
Nothing happens to them.
不许
Nothing.
这个医生已经开始怀疑我了
The doctor is suspicious.
她应该的
She should be.
你走开的时候她正在和她的州长父亲通话
She was on the line with the governor when you walked up.
你在窃听他们
You were listening.
他们俩的电话都装了窃听器
Both lines are tapped.
我们可不是菜鸟
We're not rookies.
你知道他父亲告诉她什么了?
Father tell her what you know?
你知道  不是通过电话
Not over the phone.
但是她父亲知道你是谁
But he knows who you are,
所以她也就知道了
and so does she.
本来还指望她
Seeing how she was supposed
可能会带着你找到斯科菲尔德  最终找到布伦斯
to lead you to Scofield and eventually to Burrows,
现在又回到了原点
it looks like we're back to square one.
未必
Not necessarily.
还有其他他们很在乎的人
There are other people they care about.
孩子
The kid.
至于州长...
In terms of the governor...
布伦斯的孩子  保罗
Burrows' kid, Paul.
盯着他
Focus.
唐克雷蒂州长办公室  请稍等
Governor Tancredi's office.Please hold.
唐克雷蒂州长办公室
Governor Tancredi's office.
请稍等
Hold, please.
我的父亲在里面吗?
Hey, is, is my father in?
稍等下
Just a second.
唐克雷蒂州长办公室
Governor Tancredi's office.
你好  布鲁斯 你好  莎拉
Hey, Bruce.Oh, hi, Sara.
我想见见我的父亲
I'm trying to get a hold of dad.
我希望可以联系到他
I need to reach him on his cell.
他刚下了飞机  应该快到家了
He actually just landed. Should be home soon.
好了  但是我不知道他有没有心情
Okay. I don't know if he's going to be in much of a mood
和你谈话 为什么?
to talk, though. Why?
你父亲接到了一个白宫的电话
Your father got a call from the white house.
他们停止了你父亲的州长提名
They withdrew his nomination.
什么?
What?
我2个小时前还和他通过话
I talked to him two hours ago.
他什么都没有说啊
He didn't say anything about that.
刚刚发生的
It just happened.
根据他们的说法
According to them
他的提名批准程序有问题
His confirmation was going to be a problem.
我们不是有选票吗?
We had the votes, right?
绝对多数准则(美国宪法的两个准则之一)
Super majority.
好的  那么...
Okay. So...
雷诺仕总统曾经釜底抽薪
President reynolds pulled the plug on a sure thing
就是为了重新开始
In order to start over from scratch?
像这样的事情在政治中会发生吗?
How often does something like that happen in politics?
从来没有
Never.
从什么时候开始我们成了绑匪了?
since when did we become kidnappers?
这可不好
It ain't right.
毫无疑问...
Without a doubt...
明天我们可以把良知赎回来
Well, we can buy a conscience tomorrow.
是的  是的
Yeah, well, yeah.
闭上眼睛还会不断闪现死囚区的室友
Closing your eyes ain't gonna make it go away.
我要花5分钟
I'll take five minutes
来搞定
of a situation I can control
50年也做不成的事
over 50 years of one I can't any day.
嗨  一百美元先生
Hey, mr. Hundred dollar bill.
什么信仰
Uh, what's it like being with
让非洲人长成这副德行
the african persuasion anyhow?
你他妈的给我闭嘴
You shut the hell up.
哦  有种打我啊
Oh, hit me a nerve.
为什么你不下来这个坑挖啊  伙计?
why don't you get down in that hole and dig, man?
那么你来做后备怎么样  黑鬼?
Oh, yeah. How about you backin' up, dark fella?
我们离回家还早着呢  废物
You're a long way away from home, trailer park.
我可以把你埋在那个洞里
I can put you in that hole,
甚至没有人会听到你的叫声
and nobody would ever hear you scream.
别说了
Knock it off.
我们请了安全专家马克 布诺尼
We have security expert marc bruni with us
他将解释
who will explain
其他监狱怎样确保不会重蹈福克斯河监狱
How other prisons are ensuring that they are not victimized
那8个逃犯的覆辙?
By the next Fox River eight.
应该是福克斯河监狱的7个逃犯了
Should be the Fox River seven
既然阿布鲁奇已经死了
now that Abruzzi's taken his dirt nap.
上帝当然会释放他的灵魂了
God rest the man's soul, of course.
说到数字  我们少了一个
Speaking of numbers,we're short one.
那小子去加油很长时间了
Kid's taken a long time to fill that gas tank up.
我想尽一切办法对付他
Leaned on him in every way I can think of.
他  他怎么都不肯说
He's, uh...he's not talking.
你是天主教徒吗?
Are you catholic?
那没什么用
Not much good in it.
充满了罪恶
Lot of guilt.
招供才是出路
but the one good thing is confession.
有什么事情使你烦恼
Whatever you got eating at you
你只要...
you just...
把它说出来
give it up.
我得说  感觉就会好点
Feels good, I have to say.
可能说出来
Guess it's letting it out.
让别人去倾听
Letting another human being hear it.
我对你没有什么好说的  伙计
I ain't got nothin' to say to you, man.
如果我告诉你一些事呢?
What if I told you something?
一个别人都不知道的秘密
A secret nobody else knows.
奥斯卡 肖...
Oscar Shales...
这个我追踪了几年的家伙
guy I was chasing a few years back.
聪明透顶
Smart as hell.
我...
I...
总是慢一步抓不到他
kept just missing him.
像是一场游戏  像...下棋
It became kind of a game, like, uh, chess.
那不是很有趣
Would've almost been fun
如果他没有一路杀人的话
if it weren't for the fact that he was killing people all along the way.
死的人越来越多
Bodies kept stacking up
我开始觉得就是因为我
And I started To feel that it was because of me.
因为我没有做好我的工作
Because I couldn't do my job.
我不够聪明
Because I wasn't smart enough.
永远都不能抓住他
Never did catch him,
让他跑了
but I did lose him.
当晚上我开车的时候我会看见
I saw things when I wouldld drive at night:
尸体
Bodies...
这样的噩梦让我晚上无法入睡
nightmares to the point that I couldn't sleep.
这...
It...
这个能让我完全摆脱残酷的现实
was a complete break from reality.
那是这些家伙想要的
That's what these little guys are for.
让我继续留在游戏里
To keep me in the game.
现在你知道了
So now you know.
我终于说了出来了
Now it's off my chest.
有时应该试着说出来的
Ought to try it sometime.
就像刚才我说的...
Like I said before...
我不会告诉你任何事情
I ain't gonna tell you nothin'.
你知道那些家伙在什么地方
You know where those guys are.
你如果要通过我找他们  那么伙计你找错人了
If you're looking for a rat,you got the wrong guy, man.
我只想为你减轻点罪孽
Nah, I'm just trying to spare you some guilt.
巴格威尔获得自由不到24个小时就杀了
Bagwell was free less than 24 hours
第一个受害者
before he killed his first victim.
你如果不告诉我他在那里
If you don't tell me where he is now,
他还会再杀人的
he's gonna kill again
那些血只会让你良心不安
And that blood is gonna be on your conscience
而不是别人
And nobody else's.
招供并不是件坏事  嗯?
Confession might not be such a bad thing, huh?
- 他刚到  LJ   - 不可能啊
-He just arrived, LJ. - That's impossible.
我没有约见我的律师啊
I-I don't have a meeting scheduled with my lawyer.
他是伊利诺斯州法庭指定的一个公共辩护律师
He's a court-appointed public defender in illinois.
我不确定怎么他不通知我 就来亚利桑那州找我呢
I doubt he would come to arizona without calling me.
我们走吧
Let's go.
是
yeah.
我们已经在亚利桑那州 布伦斯儿子的身边安插了人
We're all set in arizona with the Burrows kid.
好的
Good.
最好能让这小子消失
The kid's as good as gone.
你刚才说那律师叫什么?
What'd you say the name of that lawyer was?
别跟我说
Didn't give it to me.
跟监狱长去说
Gave it to the warden.
那我想和监狱长谈谈
Then I want to talk to the warden.
嘿 你听到了吗?
Hey, you hear me?
待会吧
After.
你好  LJ
hello, LJ.
你想怎样?
What do you want?
他们难道没告诉你
They didn't tell you
我为什么来这?
Why I came here?
没
No.
我是莫哈维县美国人争取民主行动组织的人
I'm an ada here in mohave county.
我来这帮你办这事
I'm here to serve you with these.
那是什么?
What are those?
释放你的文件
Your release papers.
嘿  麦特   唐克雷蒂小姐
- Hey, Matt. - Ms. Tancredi.
我爸爸在吗? 在书房
-Is my dad in?- In his study.
好的  谢谢
Great. Thank you.
嘿  爸爸?
hey, dad?
救命啊!
Help!
我得吃药
I need my pill.
请让我吃下药
Please, I need my pill.
什么?
What?
我得吃药
I need my pills.
算了吧   不  你不明白  我真的得吃药
Forget it.No, you don't understand;I need them.
是为了我的孩子
They're for my baby.
是为了防止流产的二甲双胍(降血糖药)
They're metformin to prevent a miscarriage.
求你了
Please.
在厨房的抽屉里
They're in the drawer in the kitchen.
就是那只
That one right there.
几颗?
how many?
2颗
Two.
还有水  谢谢
And water. Please.
我得把你嘴再堵上
You know I got to put the gag back on.
等下  我想问个问题
Wait, before you do,I just have one more question.
你看上去是一个好人
You seem like a really good guy.
为什么要这么做?
Why are you doing this?
我不是个好人
I'm not a good guy.
...你认为他们真的能将凶残的人
anything Changes, do you really think they'll help keep predators
诸如帝博格顺利逮捕?
like Theodore Bagwell safely behind bars?
这照片让我看起来像反社会的人
picture makes me look like a sociopath.
我不是和你开玩笑  废物
I'm not joking with you, trailer park.
马上给我来挖!
Now, get in here and dig!
我残废了  这还得谢谢你们
I am incapable, thanks to all y'all.
你给我记牢
You just remember:
是我帮你们找到这地方的!
My x marked the spot!
还记得吧
You remember that.
我们还有个麻烦  那个孩子
We got a bigger issue.The kid.
他去了多久了?
How long's it been since he left?
大概一个半小时了
An hour and a half, maybe.
花一个半小时加一箱油?
Hour and a half to fill a tank of gas?
有点不对劲 事情有了突破性的进展
that ain't right. There has been a breaking development
两起故意杀人起诉案中
In the double homicide prosecution
林肯 布伦斯 Jr
of Lincoln Burrows Jr.
由于丢失了重要的血液证据以及...
Due to the sudden disappearance of crucial blood and...
林肯  我不知道你还有个儿子
hey, Linc, I didn't know you had a boy.
鉴于此库克郡(伊利诺州)地区检察院
...Itself, the Cook county district attorney's office
迫不得已只能撤销
had no choice but to drop
对这个16岁男孩的所有指控
All chargesagainst the 16-year-old.
布伦斯按计划将于
Burrows is scheduled to be released
明日在其关押地
from the Klipton Detention Center
亚利桑那州的克利普顿拘留中心
in Kingman, Arizona,
被释放
where he's currently being held, tomorrow morning.
车钥匙呢  在哪里?
keys to the car--where are they?
你不能这么做  林肯
You can't do this. Linc.
只要再5分钟就行了
We're five minutes away in there.
我们这样都已经弄了4个小时了
We've been five minutes for four hours.
再给我点时间  耐心点
Just give me some time. Be patient.
你以为我不想挖到那该死的钱?
You think I give a damn about the money?
我别无选择!
I'm doing what's necessary!
你害怕失败
You're afraid to fail--
你害怕这个宏伟的计划不能成功
you're afraid this big plan of yours ain't gonna work out.
如果为了证明你能成功而最后被抓住
You want to get caught proving you can
那随便你
pull this thing off, be my guest.
LJ被释放了  我要去接他
LJ's out there;I'm gonna get him.
我们已经走了1500英里
We have come 1, 500 miles
穿越了全国
across the country.
我们已经
We have made it
走到了这一步
this far.
那我想我们得在这分道扬镳了
Then I guess this is where we part ways.
审讯有进展吗?
Any word of how  the interrogation's going?
那孩子还是什么都不说
Nah, the kid's  still stonewalling,
但我们有了帕托塞克确切的消息
but we've got confirmation on Patoshik;
那老太太的家里到处都是他的指纹
his prints were all over that old lady's house.
他没拿钱也没拿珠宝
So he leaves the cash and the jewelry.
只拿走了那幅值10美元的油画
The only thing he steals is a ten-dollar oil painting.
这家伙他妈搞什么鬼?
What the hell's wrong with that?
有什么我可以帮忙的吗?
is there something I can help you with?
什么?不  要知道
what?No.You know
用推车装那些东西会容易点
it'd be a little easier if you use the cart for all that stuff.
我只是想  我想...看看这个袋子能否装下
I'm just, uh, I wanted to...see if it'd all fit in the bag.
你的膝盖怎么了?
what happened to your knee there?
摩托车事故
Motorcycle accident.
你行动不太方便  是吧?
you don't move around too well, then, do you?
是不太方便
Not very.
那好
That's good.
你可以跟我一起走
you can still come with me.
不  我...
No, I can...
我自己能行
I can do this.
那如果不行呢?
And if you can't?
那我们还是在
Then we still meet up
约定好的地方见  波修瓦 波兹 (可能是美国边境线往墨西哥去的一条小路)
exactly where we planned.Bolshee Booze.
波修瓦
Bolshoi.
LJ会和我一起的
LJ's going to be with me.
知道怎么去那吗?
You remember how to get there?
怎么会忘呢?
How can I forget?
星期四晚上6点
Thursday night, 6:00.
那是我们最后的机会
It's our last shot.
如果我们  呃...
If we're, uh...
如果一切顺利的话
if we do this right
我们就可以永远离开这
we're gone forever.
三天时间还有很多事要干
Lot of ground to cover in three days.
很多
Lot of ground.
是的
好吧
All right.
保重
Take care.
他们会追捕你的
They'll be gunning for you.
他们会想尽一切办法抓你  所以...
They'll get you any way they can, so...
是的
yep.
告诉LJ...
Tell LJ...
告诉他  我会送一块
tell him I said there'll be
写着他名字的冲浪板给他
A surfboard with his name on it.
好的
Nice.
波修瓦 波兹
Bolshoi Booze.
三天后
Three days.
小心点
Keep your head down.
唐克雷蒂小姐
Ms.Tancredi...
你好
hi.
我只是想告诉你
I just wanted to let you know that
法医已经初步检验了尸体
the me-- she's finished her preliminary examination of the body.
她发现
She found
没有谋杀迹象
no signs of foul play.
我知道这对你是个打击
I know it's a shock
但我们已经问过外面的安全人员
but we've also spoken to the detail guard stationed outside
他说从华盛顿回来后除了你父亲
and he didn't see anyone other than your father
就没有任何人
enter or exit the mansion
进出过这栋大楼
since he came back from Washington.
我父亲是不会自杀的
My father is not a suicidal man.
还有没有其他亲人
Look, is there any extended family
我应该去通知的
I should call?
我们家只有我一个孩子  我母亲去世了
I'm an only child. My mother passed away.
我想一个人冷静一下  好吗?
Could I have a moment, please?
好的
Yeah.
这可是一笔很划算的交易  孩子
that's a hell of a good deal, son.
我是说  不会因为你越狱
I mean, we're talking no additional time
再给你加刑
on your sentence for the escape.
你要是需要  我可以给你书面证明
You want it in writing, I'll put it in writing.
我们会送你到联邦俱乐部(高级监狱)
We will put you up at club fed
在那你可以跟股票经纪人还有律师
and you'll spend your days playing racquetball
一起玩壁球
with stockbrokers and lawyers.
四年后你就可以重获自由了
Four years from now you'll be out on the street,
22岁没有犯罪纪录
22 years old with a clean slate
你的前途就摆在你面前
and your whole life ahead of you,
清清白白
and no blood on your hands.
怎么样?
Okay?
那房里有个女人
There's a woman in the house.
如果你们的人出现的话
If you guys show up...
她就会成为人质
it's just going to turn her into a hostage.
帝博格
T-bag
他不能活着出来
he ain't coming out alive.
但他会跟那女人同归于尽
And he's going to take her with him.
这些事你就不用担心了
Let me worry about that.
不  可不能这么说
No, hell, no.
唯一能让那女人活着出来的办法
The only way that that woman comes out free
就是让个他们信任的人
is if someone shows up on that porch
出现在那门口
that they trust.
你?
Being you?
是我
Being me.
我会带你去找他们
I'll take it.
你喜欢这?
You like it?
你喜欢牛肉干...你喜欢牛肉干?
You like it, jerky?
你喜欢牛肉干
You like jerky.
你为什么坐牢
What were you in for?
我不想谈这事  小姐
I don't want to talk, lady.
我在自己家里成了犯人
I'm a prisoner in my own house.
至少让我
Least you could offer me
跟你聊聊吧
is a little conversation.
好吧
All right.
我要是猜对了就告诉我
Just let me know when I hit it.
谋杀?
Murder?
强奸?绑架?
Rape?Kidnapping?
性虐待?
Sexual abuse?
儿童性虐待?
Child sexual abuse?
一般性抢劫
Aggravated robbery.
你被判了几年?
How long were you doing?
5年
Five years.
还有多久的刑期?
How much longer did you have left to serve?
18个月
18 months.
那你为什么
Why on earth would you
越狱...
break out of prison with...
那女的叫什么名字?
What's her name?
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
她跟别的男人跑了?
So what, she was running away with another man?
听着  也许你应该让她走  而不是...
Look, maybe you should have let her go rather instead of...
她怀了我的孩子
she's having my baby.
她怀了多久了?
How far along is she?
我不想谈这个
I don't want to talk about it.
我怀孕两个月了
I'm two months.
星期二我做了第一次B超检查
I just had my first trimester sonogram on tuesday.
各单位注意10-5号紧急通知
10-5 dispatch to all units.
她给你看了孩子的照片吗?
Has she shown you pictures of...
联邦调查局正在押送大卫 阿克斯  准备行动
Transporting David Apolskis in FBI custody. Stand by.
这得要挖上一整天
Yo, this is going to take all day.
我们需要多点人手
We need more manpower.
你要知道  站在一旁叽叽歪歪
You know, standing around jabbering
不会把这泥
ain't gonna get the dirt
从地里挖出来
out of that ground.
你这个混蛋
Son of a bitch
我们得马上离开
We got to roll.
为什么?
Why?
对讲机广播  那小子被抓了
They got tweener. It was on the radio.
跟你们在一起真是倒霉
Nice knowing y'all.
他们提到我们在哪了没?
They say anything about where we are?
我没时间听
I'm not hanging around to find out.
也许你应该听听
Well, maybe you should.
也许你真应该听听
Maybe you should.
或许我们都该
Maybe we all should.
我们来确认一下
Let's go over this again.
他们身上都没携带武器?
None of them are armed?
枪?没有
With guns-- no.
巴格威尔只有螺丝刀之类的工具
Bagwell had a screwdriver or something.
我们真的得这样么?
Do we really need this, man?
是的
Yeah.
以防你做蠢事
In case you decide to do something stupid
比如暗示他们逃走
like tip them off.
你知不知道那里是哪儿?
You know what I talked?
荷兰
Holland.
我要住在风车里
I'm going to live in a windmill.
我们只需要一个木筏
All we need is a raft.
我现在就去造一个
I'm going to build it.
就从这根...
It all starts with this...
不  这根木棍开始
no, this stick.
查尔斯 韦斯特莫兰德   上帝保佑你和你的皱麻袋
Charles Westmoreland, god bless you and your wrinkled old sack.
都在这儿了
it's all here.
我欠你一句深深的感谢  帅哥
I owe you a profound thanks, pretty.
几天后
A couple days from now,
我就带着口袋里的一百万美元
I'm going to be walking down the streets of bangkok
走在曼谷的大街上了
with a million us in my pocket.
换成泰铢就有四千万
That's about 40 million baht in the local currency.
伙计  你去泰国干什么?
Man, what the hell is up with you and thailand, huh?
黑市外科手术  匿名器官捐献者
Black market surgery, anonymous transplant donors
他和她穿的都一样  还有什么不一样的?
"he"s dressed like "she"s-- what's there not to like?
你真的要去换只手?
Are you really going to try to replace that hand?
我的身体不要这只
Body ain't takin' to this one.
难以置信
unbelievable.
好吧  快收拾吧
All right, let's move.
你知道  那只手不会是白人的
You know, that hand ain't gonna be white.
什么?
What?
新的那只手
The new one.
即使你到了那里  那也不会是白人的手
Even if you get down there, it ain't gonna be white.
一个3K党居然长了只亚洲人的手
hey, Johnny KKK over here is going to have an asian hand.
不许出错  让我们彻底抓住他们
No mistakes. Let's get them clean.
我要知道
I need to know
我能否相信你
if I can trust him.
他们正在计划越狱
they're escaping.
快走吧
Now walk.
- 斯科特... - 我没有太多时间
Scott... -I don't got much time, all right.
我必须告诉你一些事情  狗娘养的
I had to tell you something. Son of A...
那天在汽车旅馆你为我所做的...
what you did for me that day at the motel...
...在我生命中从没有人那样对我
ain't nobody in my life has been to bat for me like that.
但是我骗了你
And I lied to you.
双手放在头上  跪下  我的名字不是斯科特
Hands on your head.Get on your knees!My name isn't Scott.
快跪下!   我的名字是大卫
My name is Dave.
大卫 阿克斯  跪下!
Dave Apolskis. - Get down!
我只是...
And I just...
我只想让你知道
I wanted you to know.
因为我会写信给你的
Because I'm gonna be writing you.
而且我会万分期待你能回信
And I sure as hell hope that you write back.
我能帮你什么?
Can I help you?
对不起  我认识你吗?
I'm sorry.Do I know you?
承办人
Contractor.
有些电路问题
We got some electrical issues.
不  不  你不能帮到什么
No, you can't help me.
抱歉  有问题吗?
Excuse me.Is there a problem?
欧文斯女士现在不在家
Ms.Owens is not home.
是的  好  我是来接去她去俱乐部的
Yeah, well, I'm supposed to drive her to the club...
她已经去了
she already went to the club.
是的  她刚出去时
Yeah, um, she came out
说她去俱乐部
said she was going to the club.
她自己开车走了
She got into her car and left.
其他我就不知道了
I don't know what else to tell you.
好吧  谢谢
Yeah.Okay, thanks.
他走了
he's gone.
我们马上离开这里
We got to get out of here.
因为他一到俱乐部
'Cause once he gets to the club
发现她不在那儿
he's going to find out she's not there.
就会回来
Then he's going to be back.
你知道吗?
Know what?
你是对的
You were right.
把心里的东西说出来
It does feel good
就是会感觉好很多
to get stuff off your chest.
对不起
I'm sorry
我那样耍你  兄弟
I had to play you like that, bro.
喔  怎么了?
Yo, what's up?
来  还要开很久
Come on.It's going to be a long drive.
活动一下你的腿
Stretch your legs.
好的
All right.
克里曼
Kellerman.
我以为你处理好 LJ 布伦斯的事了
I thought you were going to deal with the LJ Burrows situation.
哦  是的
Oh, I did.
那为什么他明天会被释放?
Then why is he being released from Custody tomorrow?
不释放  那孩子对我们
In and of himself
就没有利用价值
the kid is useless to us.
他唯一的价值就是谁会去接他
His only value lies in who comes looking for him.
还有  更重要的
More importantly, though
唐克雷蒂州长...
Governor Tancredi...
不在我们计划之内
not part of our plan.
上次我查到你留下了些蛛丝马迹
Last time I checked, you left no shortage of bodies in your wake.
不  我为了凯若琳做了我该做的
No, I did what I had to do to get Caroline where she is.
现在她已经成功了
Now that she's there
我们不用花太多精力在这上面
let's not draw any more attention than we have to.
你以为帮她当上总统是最难的?
You think getting to the top is the hard part?
她现在显眼一百倍
She's a hundred times more visible
就多一百倍的敌人
has a hundred times more enemies.
任何知道蛛丝马迹的人都不能放过
Anyone who knows anything has got to be dealt with.
如果有些人成了累赘  就除掉
If someone is a liability, they go.
唐克雷蒂现在成了累赘
Tancredi was becoming a liability.
他女儿也是
So was his daughter.
等等  什么?
Wait. What?
莎拉?
Sara?
再见  保罗
Bye, Paul
你现在和那些人一起逃出去
You walk out that door with those guys right now
你们迟早会被抓住
and it's only a matter of time before you get caught.
你很清楚  对吗?
You realize that, don't you?
你们不仅会被指控越狱
You're not just gonna be dealing with escape charges
还有故意伤害
but assault
非法禁锢
unlawful imprisonment
绑架... 现在我不想听到这些
kidnapping...I don't need to hear this right now.
哦  不  你要听
Oh, no, you do.
你认为你们
How much longer do you really think
能坚持多久?
you can stay ahead of the cops?
想想  如果你告发他们
Look, if you turn yourself in
我会为你出庭作证
I will testify at the sentencing.
我会说你配合警方
I will say that you cooperated
那样就会完全不同
That can make a huge difference.
闭嘴
Shut up.
聪明点
Be smart.
你还有个孩子
You have a baby on the way.
你想在他2岁生日的时候见到他
Do you want to be around for its second birthday
还是在22岁的时候?   闭嘴
or its 22nd? -Shut up.
如果你不想听这些
If you didn't want to hear what I had to say
如果你不想听你正在犯一个大错
if you didn't want to hear what a big mistake you're making,
你刚才就可以塞住我的嘴
you would've put that gag back on me...
费尔南多
Fernando!
是时候离开这儿了  我们走吧
Time to get out of here.Let's go.
你现在还可以做出正确的选择 费尔南多
You can still do the right thing, Fernando.
看啊  瞧瞧
Look-a-here, look-a-here.
瞧瞧
Look-a-here.
装点零钱
Pocket change.
当你在里兹大饭店
In case you want to tip the valet
想给小费的时候会用的上
when you're at the Ritz.
是啊  这正是我想说的
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about, boy.
苏克雷在哪儿?
Where's Sucre?
在这里
Right here.
你干什么?
What are you doing?
放下包
Drop the bag.
谁都别想走
No one's going anywhere.
就像你知道  我不想
Just so you know, man
和那些人混在一起
I'm not gonna roll on those guys.
我不会那样做了  那...
It ain't gonna happen, so...
如果是为了关于...
if that's what this is about...
我们早前谈论的是
we were talking about
招供
confession earlier.
嗯...
And, uh...
我得跟你道歉
I think I owe you an apology
因为我骗了你...
because I lied to you...
...关于奥斯卡 肖
about Oscar Shales.
他一直逼我  然后我...
Smart-ass just kept pushing it, and I...
我紧咬着他不放
I snapped.
这里
Right there.
就是子弹打中的地方
That's where I put the bullet in him.
我不关心这些
I don't care about none of this.
错就错在  记住前车之鉴
Mistake about that is forensics will tell the whole tale.
火药灼伤
Powder burns.
枪对准他的头
The gun was right against his head.
长官...
Sir...
我想我们还是回...
I think we should go back to...
看  还是坦白比较好吧  你知道
see, that's what's good about confession, you know,
因为你说把心里的东西说出来...
'cause you say something, you get it off your chest and...
现在全世界都知道了
it just goes out there into the whole world.
我很遗憾  孩子
And I'm so sorry about this, kid
因为我真的希望你明白
because I really hope you understand.
我不会怪罪你  孩子
I got nothing against you, kid.
你要做什么?
What are you doing, man?
但子弹会
But they do.